myfdb.com 2014-10-09

# Privacy Policy - MyFDB

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact MyFDB via electronic mail at [info@myfdb.com](mailto:info@myfdb.com) or by mail directed to: 

My Fashion Database, LLC  
Attn: Privacy Policy Questions 17530 Ventura Boulevard, Suite 201  
Encino, California 91316 

## Information we may gather from you

When you visit www.MyFDB.com, we may collect information about your visit. We may collect your IP address (or the address of your proxy), browser type, domain name, and we may log the length of time of your visit and the number of times you visit and your manner of use of this site. By using this site, you expressly permit us to collect and use the information we collect from you. 

Generally, electronic information of this nature is used to gather non-specific demographic information about our visitors and generally such information is used to personalize the information you see displayed on this site. To the extent provided, your IP address may also be used to help identify your computer so that we can make your visit to our site more enjoyable. Your IP address (or the address of your proxy) is not at all linked to any personal identifiable information. 

Depending on the nature of your visit to this site, we may collect your contact information (including, for example, your email address) and, to the extent applicable, if you are making a purchase from us and/or a payment through this site, we will require you to provide us with billing and financial information (like your address, phone number and credit account or credit card number). We may use third parties to verify and authorize credit card transactions made through this site. The billing address and phone number you provide will generally only be used for verification purposes, while your email address may be used for multiple purposes, including, verification, log in and mailing lists. 

We may use your contact information to send you information about additional offers or services. Additionally, depending on the nature of your visit, you may ask us to store information on certain listings posted on this site. In such cases, we may share your personal and contact information with our team of agents and affiliates to more properly service you. 

We may use cookies to store information. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are text files that are commonly deposited by sites on a user’s hard drive. The file identifies a user’s computer and can record a user’s preferences and certain other information. Generally, cookies make it easier for you to interact with a site. You may be able to prevent our collection of such data by setting your browser to reject cookies but blocking cookies may adversely affect your ability to interact with this site. You may be able to find your own cookie files on your hard disk and see what information is being stored in such files and by which sites and may be able to delete information contained in such cookie files. To find a cookie file, search for cookie.txt, or cookies. 

## Security

We use our reasonable efforts to protect the data we collect from you against unauthorized access. When you buy a subscription or place orders, we offer the use of a secure socket layer (SSL). You may be able to discern whether your information is being transmitted via SSL by making certain that the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) is prefixed with “https” rather than “http” and that a padlock icon is displayed on the lower right corner of your browser (for transmissions via MS Internet Explorer 7.0). The cost of subscription to www.myfdb.com is, $14.99/month USD. If you make a payment through this site, you may be directed to a third party site for payment processing or verification; the policies of such third party site may apply to the processing of your transaction. We are not responsible for the policies of any third party sites. We do not currently offer any refunds or returns, all purchases are final. 

## Correct/Update

During the transaction process, we will endeavor to permit you to review, change, or delete the information that you have submitted. We encourage you to update your information whenever it changes. 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  * By logging into your account at www.myfdb.com.
  * You can send email to [info@myfdb.com](mailto:info@myfdb.com)
  * You can send mail to the following postal address:  My Fashion Database, LLC  
Attn: Customer Information Update  
17530 Ventura Boulevard, Suite 201  
Encino, California 91316  

We welcome your questions and comments. Please send e-mails to [info@myfdb.com](mailto:info@myfdb.com). 

## Privacy Changes

Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will make reasonable commercial efforts to promptly post a notice on this site indicating that new information has been posted. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will take reasonable commercial efforts to promptly notify you by way of email. To the extent practicable, we will endeavor to offer you a choice as to whether or not we use information previously collected in a different manner. We will take reasonable commercial efforts to use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

## Required Disclosure of Information

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may be required to disclose personal information pursuant to applicable law. We will make such disclosure when we believe that such disclosure or other action is necessary to comply with applicable law, legal process served on us or in connection with any investigation. We also reserve the right to disclose personal information to protect our rights and property, including, without limitation, in connection with any investigation of fraud we believe to be necessary and to otherwise protect the users of this site and others. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about the terms, provisions and conditions set forth herein, our practices, or your dealings with this site, please feel free to contact us at: 

My Fashion Database, LLC  
17530 Ventura Boulevard, Suite 201  
Encino, California 91316  
info@MyFDB.com  

Last modified: May 8, 2009
